Guide to the NWYM Memorial collection 1889-2003
George Fox University and Northwest Yearly Meeting of Friends Archives
NWYM Memorials collection
1889-2003
George Fox University and Northwest Yearly Meeting of Friends Archives 416 North Meridian Street Newberg, Oregon 97132 archives@georgefox.edu http://www.georgefox.edu/offices/murdock/Archives/index.html
Northwest Yearly Meeting of Friends Church
NWYM.01.26
0.5 cubic feet held in a document box
Written memorials for passed members of the Northwest Yearly Meeting and Oregon Yearly Meeting from 1889-2003.
Accession Legacy.812
This collection is available for use.
This collection contains written memorials and eulogies for members of the Northwest Yearly Meeting of Friends/Oregon Yearly Meeting from 1889-2003.
Northwest Yearly Meeting of Friends Church; Funerals; Quakers
Religion
- 1889, 1/1
  Parker, Eva
- 1910, 1/2
  Moon, Anna Lowe, Mrs.
- 1918, 1/3
  Binford, Isaac Sumner; Binford, Minnie J.; Cook, Florence E. Hinshaw; Mills, Rhoda Jane Hester; Mills, Henry; Jones, Eli; Jones, Edna Bedinger
- 1922, 1/4
  Woodward, Ezra H.; Minthorn, Henry John, Dr.; Hammer, Phebe Minthorn; Baldwin, Charles
- 1923, 1/5
  Gidley, Dorwin; Edwards, Mary E. K.
- 1924, 1/6
  Barnes, Harriet Polen; Edwards, Jesse
- 1925-1927, 1/7
  Williams, Malinda B. Hunt; Sherman, Orlando; Cammack, Ralph M.; Hinshaw, Benjamin Franklin; Kenworthy, Oliver N.; Elliott, Wilbur; Terrell, Esther Brown Lewis; Roberts, Mary Elizabeth Bevan; Williams, Floyd; Round, Louisa Painter
- 1928, 1/8
  Martin, Evangeline
- 1930, 1/9
  Rees, William
- 1933, 1/10
  Cook, John Jay
- 1934, 1/11
  Wiley, Nate Lorenzo; Jackson, Katherine Sofia
- 1936, 1/12
  Smith, Robert C.; Butler, Maude Haworth
- 1938, 1/13
  Jones, Myrta Eliza
- 1939, 1/14
  Roberts, Frank D.; Chilson, Arthur
- 1940, 1/15
  Beeson, Rhoda; Hadley, Chester A.
- 1941, 1/16
  Williams, Owen Ronald; Taylor, Hanna B.; Mills, Preston
- 1942, 1/17
  Landcaster, Anderson L.; Parker, Charles William
- 1943, 1/18
  Hinshaw, Cecil F.; Hester, Thomas W.; Maris, Isabel Osborn Kenworthy
- 1944, 1/19
  Tamplin, Effie Ramsey; Smith, Rebecca Webb Hinchman; Cammack, Helen
- 1945, 1/20
  Brown, Lottie M.; Smith, Lillie Bell Hylton
- 1946, 1/21
  Sanders, Levi; Woodward, Amanda; Rees, Lucy H.; Mills, Minerva Emma Sharp
- 1947, 1/22
  Wheeler, Eli; Gulley, Alva S.
- 1948, 1/23
  Jessup, Carey; Lowe, James Francis
- 1949, 1/24
  Miles, Anna Elizabeth Cook Bell
- 1950, 1/25
  Haines, George Emmor
- 1951, 1/26
  Blair, Anna Hobson
- 1952, 1/27
  Hodgin, Emma Mendenhall
- 1953, 1/28
  Wiles, Richard; Philpott, William; Lewis, Marietta Mills; Cammack, Mary Roby Stroud
- 1954, 1/29
  Antrim, Anna
- 1956, 1/30
  Newby, Ray Samuel
- 1957, 1/31
  Wellons, Maude; Tucker, Amanda; Street, Leela; Strait, Ferris L.; Rohrer, Pearl Koogle; Replogle, Nora K.; Morris, Clara Pearl Miller; Moon, Roy; Elliott, Marguerite Price; Farner, Flossie; Flynn, Edith Knight; Gulley, Nora A.; Haughton, Herbert
- 1958, 1/32
  Strait, Glenn; Smith, Jeraldine; Rogers, Alison; Porter, Benjamin F.; Hanson, Stanford Lewis; Haworth, Dayton D.
- 1959, 1/33
  Sand, Lenna; Ricketts, Ada; Nordyke, Robert E.; Meyers, Minnie Louelle; Merriss, Paul Adron; Gustafson, Charles; Bates, Lesta Ellen Cook
- 1960, 1/34
  Jones, Flora; McCracken, Lucille Frieda; Frazier, John; Hendricks, Lillie M.
- 1961, 1/35
  Smith, Charles F.; Cunningham, Irena B.
- 1964, 1/36
  Braithwaite, Elizabeth
- 1965, 1/37
  Carey, Gervais
- 1966, 1/38
  Hanson, Florence
- 1969, 1/39
  Haldy, Arthur John
- 1970, 1/40
  Gregory, Dean; Coffin, Merrill
- 1971, 1/41
  Ogle, Sam
- 1972, 1/42
  White, J. Alden; Keach, Maude Ramsey; Cook, Nathan Mendenhall; Hadley, Allen; Haldy, Elizabeth Mott
- 1973, 1/43
  McCracken, Joseph; Tuning, Charles; Smith, Maude; Moon, Rosella, Mrs.
- 1975, 1/44
  Caulson, Edgar Worth, Sr.
- 1976, 1/45
  Randle, George Barton
- 1977, 1/46
  Thomas, Clyde (Missionary); Jones, Gertrude T. Owens
- 1978, 1/47
  Swanson, Audrey L. Fellow; Shattuck, Willard Robert; Macy, Herman
- 1979, 1/48
  Reece, Pearl; Weesner, Oliver; Haines, Marie; Macy, Herman; Potter, Edgar Lewis; Raymond, James; Reece, Real; Alderton, Gwen; Armstrong, Hubert; Arnett, Elva; Brandenburgh, Wilbur; Cashman, Elizabeth; Casteel, Vera; Chadderton, Lewis G.; Chittick, Peter; Cook, Cleola; Elmer, Irma; Field, Cyrus W.; Finney, George; Fitch, Karla Mae; Gerstacker, Carrie Menard; Haines, Marie; Haworth, David; Hockett, Lynn; Holmes, Cornelia; King, Grace; Lewellyn, Pauline; Liedke, Ethel B.; Loop, Lila Newby; Macy, Preston P.; Macy, Ruth; Meliza, Earl; Michelson, Eva; Newby, Tom; Nordyke, LeVerne; Patzer, George; Post, Gertrude; Potter, Florence; Price, Henrietta; Pruitt, David; Richey, Milton; Sanders, Orpah; Scarburry, Ruth; Seeley, Marie; Slocum, Gail; Steiger, George; Stevens, Marie; Swanson, Audrey L. Fellow; Talbert, Edith; Thomas, Jack; Weesner, Oliver; West, Homer; Brown, Clayton S.; Brown, Louella Beals
- 1980, 1/49
  Cossell, Richard
- 1981, 1/50
  DeLapp, Lester; Barnett, Paul; Cattell, Everett; Porter, Miller; Peterson, Martin; DeLapp, Erma; Frazier, Helen; Craven, Everett; Weesner, Marge; Brown, Mildred H.; Beebe, Glen; Alger, Zarilda T.; Gulley, Emmett W.; Ross, Clifton
- 1982, 1/51
  Morgan, Anna; Miller, Gordon; Harmon, Howard E.; Butler, Mary; Carr, Cyril F.
- 1983, 1/52
  Almquist, Paul; Coffin, Anna; Dejmal, Alan Russell; Duncan, Lee; Hayden, Elizabeth Ann; Larsen, Harry; Meredith, Ralph; Nowak, Kathleen; Price, Maude; Towery, Jeanne Marie; Trefren, Hiram Donald; Winslow, Verlin
- Notes of Charles Beals on Memorials, 1984; 1/53; Beals, Charles
- 1984, 1/54
  Barker, Earl P., Dr.; Hester, Homer; Rinard, Harlan; Hayden, Elizabeth Ann; Cook, Gladys Hadley, Mrs.; Cook, Gertrude; Dicus, Lena; Pearson, John Howard; Kern, Amelia F.; Mills, Dillon; Perry, Paul D.; Soules, Ida; Duncan, Lee; Dillon, Harry
- 1985, 1/55
  Ross, Milo; Olsen, Rudolph; Hester, Homer; Cook, Gladys Hadley, Mrs.; Beebe, Fannie Mable Nutting
- 1986-1988, 1/56
  Anderson, Phyllis; Baker, Irene; Barnes, Annabel; Bright, Pauline; Cloud, Ruby; Cook, Dalton; Coulsen, Alice; Dunagan, Josephine; Dunning, Mabel; Emry, Iva; Finley, Opal; French, Arthur; Gustafson, Lois; Hadley, Ivan; Hanson, Honor; Helm, Eldon; Lawver, Lela; Lewis, John; Liebnow, Kurt E.; Miller, Vera C.; Muhr, Julia; Newman, Marie; Nilssen, Florence; Purdum, Gladys; Rector, Ruth; Robert, Alvin; Smith, Cloyd; Stanfield, Ida; Templer, Earl; Tuning, Donna; Ware, Ted; Welch, Iona; Wight, Bessie; Kimball, Mildred; Kliewer, Karen Cook; Knight, Roy; Knutson, Gladys; Lamm, Charles J.; Lewis, Robert Riley; Lute, Shirley Zoller; Macy, Margaret Rose; Cooper, Ray; Sholfield, William Earl; Coulson, Alice Mendenhall Roberts; Liebnow, Pearl E.; Liebnow, Kurt E.; Howard, Linda; Hodson, Harold; Larrance, Lindley; Smith, Veva; Smith, Eugene; Perisho, Chloe Hibbs; Myers, Myrtle Brightup; Tuning, Michael; Terwilleger, Lucy; Wilhite, Walter; Edwards, Gerald Jesse
- 1987, 1/57
  McKee, Alta Mae; Pierson, Doyle; Stevens, George; Steen, Iola; Hoffman, Audrey; Judd, Vyonne; Kelley, Truman Orville (Tio); Craven, Chaline T. Shew; Armstrong, Barbara; Davis, Thelma Ruby; Barnett, Alice M.; Bradley, Eldridge Lincoln; Cattell, Halley; Swanson, John Emel; Morse, Richard M.; Folwell, Ethel; Smith, Isaac Alonzo; Harmon, Velda L.; Lewis, Joyce Perisho; Ellis, Bill; Baker, Frederick Belmont; Cook, Walter Camille; Porter, Hazel; Tamplin, Carroll; Baird, Ted; Barker, Adelaide; Bradley, Eldridge Lincoln; Bridger, Grace; Cattell, Catherine; Cattell, Halley; Colby, Opal; Cooper, Ray; Crosby, Irene; Davis, Thelma Ruby; Edmundson, Mary; Edwards, Gerard; Ellis, Maxine; Eshelman, Shaun David; Ewing, Bonnie; Folwell, Ethel; Harmon, Velda L.; Hodson, Harold; Howard, Clare; Howard, Linda; Johnson, Jerry; Kemper, Eugene; Knutson, Gladys; Larrance, Lindley; Lewis, Joyce Perisho; Moore, Marvin; Morse, Richard M.; Meyers, Myrtle; Pearson, Emma; Perisho, Chloe Hibbs; Ralphs, Ethel; Reed, Carma; Richey, Sterling; Schwartz, Henry; Schofield, Earl; Smith, Eugene; Smith, Isaac Alonzo; Smith, Veva; Swanson, John Emel; Terwilleger, Lucy; Thatcher, Ruby; Thomas, Harry; Trefren, Shirley; Tuning, Michael; Wilhite, Walter; Willcuts, Beulah; Williams, Estelle May
- 1988, 1/58
  Kimball, Mildred; Kliewer, Karen Cook; Knight, Roy; Lamm, Charles J.; Lewis, Robert Riley; Lute, Shirley Zoller; Macy, Margaret Rose; Mills, Betty M.; Pierson, Hazel Jeffery; Puckett, Cyril; Vermillion, Wallace Albert; Snow, Marynette; Baker, Melva; Beals, Mildred; Carpenter, Kay; Carroll, Alice; Collver, Lloyd; Corbin, Ruth; Davis, Vern; Engeman, Wendell; Griffiths, Mary Ellen; Johnson, Clarence; Kimball, Mildred; Lewis, Robert; Roberts, Marie Coffin; Sandoz, Winifred Woodward; Vermillion, Wallace Albert; Ellis, Bill; Knight, Roy; Springer, Edna; Steen, Iola; Baker, Verna; Berry, Jess; Bishop, Elizabeth; Blake, Freda; Chandler, Lillian Rowlett; Clark, Harold; Combes, Martha; Cook, Jake; Cook, Nettie; Craven, Charlene; Crisman, Edmund; Curry, Ethel; Davis, Elmer; Devaul, Marie Gregory Pop; Elliott, Nola; Ferrell, Mary E.; Fink, Stella; Ireland, Elsie; Fullerton, Margaret; Hadley-Voth, Marilyn; Hanson, David; Hart, Eva; Haworth, Hanson; Hill, Donald; Hoffman, Audrey; Irvin, Mary Ellen; Johnson, Lucille; Judd, Frank; Kaufman, Pearl; Kelley, Truman Orville (Tio); Leighty, Kenneth; Lewis, Erma; Macy, Mary Alice; Madel, Timothy; Mannen, Charles; Martin, Ruby; McDonald, Gladys; McKee, Alta Mae; McNichols, Freda; Mills, Betty M.; Meyers, Wendell; Powell, William; Ramsey, Shirley; Rempel, Reba; Rist, Howard; Schmoe, Geary; Sivley, Richard; Snow, Marynette; Strayer, Zula; Terwilleger, Henry; Valentine, Carsen; Wadley, Thelma; West, Lillian; Whisler, Winifred; Pierson, Hazel Jeffery; Davis, Vern; Macy, Margaret Rose; Lewis, Robert; Collver, Lloyd; Beals, Mildred; Groves, Jannie; Beals, Ellis H.; Johnson, Clarence; Fewless, Beulah; Harris, Jim; Baker, Melva; Overby, Erling; Overby, Marie; Sandoz, Winifred Woodward; Judd, Vyonne; Hansen, David Donald; Griffiths, Mary Ellen; Davis, Verne O.; Corbin, Ruth; Collver, Lloyd
- 1989, 1/59
  Baker, Melva; Moore, Emily R.; Roberts, Marie Coffin; Rudisill, Sybil O.; Willcuts, Jack; Beebe, Richard; Beals, Charles; Kim, Kwan Kyu; Asher, George; Baker, Russell; Bently, Lila; Brougher, Esther; Byer, Louise; Canoose, Cleo; Carlton, Herman; Cossell, Esther; Daniels, Harry A.; Deich, Frank; Ditch, Floyd; Dobson, Georgana; Farinas, Lorena; Fleck, Mildred Parker; Frazier, Clara; Goldsmith, Beatrice; Hanson, William Edwin; Hardinger, Cecil; Hathaway, Rachel; Headrick, Ruth; Herrick, Ruth; Haines, Marie; Hofstetter, Truman; Holton, Lela; Holton, Roger; Ireland, George; Kaiser, Vinita; Keller, Lester; Knauss, Wilmer "Bill"; Lewis, Charles "Ted"; Lingenfelter, Leonard; Logan, Richard; Marks, Leland; Martin, Blanche; Meliza, Orba; Moor, Edith; Palmer, Ruth; Palmgren, Irene; Parker, Lucille; Roberts, Phyllis; Rose, Thelma; Rudisill, Sybil O.; Street, Helen; Sweet, William M.; VanDerhoff, Lois; Voth, Elver; Walters, Fred; Williams, Leta; Williams, Raymond; Wilson, Helen; Yerson, Ralph; Sandoz, Winifred Woodward; Engeman, Wendell; Carroll, Alice; Carpenter, Kay; Blodgett, Dwain
- 1990, 1/60
  McConaughey, Clarence L.; Williams, Leta; Hull, Vera D.; Bolitho, Geneva; Benham, Robert LeRoy, Sr.; Brooks, Amy; Baker, Nellie; Blodgett, Dwain; Brain, Melvin; Campbell, Alice; Canale, Frank; Cassman, Nettie; Clark, Ruth; Cobb, Doris; Colby, Charles C.; Comfort, Edith; Cordier, Margaret; Cramm, Benjamin; Craven, E. Glenn; Davenport, Melvin; Dorman, Bernard; Edmunson, Donald; Edner, Mildred; Ellis, Helen; Evans, Gladys; Farinas, Lorena; Griffith, Ethel; Hanson, Elroy; Haworth, Rachel; Hockett, Elsie; Hull, Vera D.; Hunt, Esther; Huston, Marguerite Johnson; Jerome, Mark; Lamm, Charles J.; Lingenfelter, Leonard; Lucas, George; Mardock, Wendell; May, Mattie; McConaughey, Clarence L.; Mitchell, Olive; Mylander, Ellwood; Neher, Galen; Olsen, Esther; Olson, Al; Parker, Floyd; Salazar, Jesse; Sanders, Ivan; Schwartz, Charlotte; Sherman, May; Shook, Mamie M.; Tycksen, Nute; Whittier, Thelma; Yergen, Blanche Elizabeth; Hunt, M. Esther; Hockett, Elsie; Goldsmith, Beatrice; Campbell, Alice; Davenport, Melvin; Mardock, Wendell; Rhoe, Cloyd
- 1991, 1/61
  Lamm, Charles J.; Tuning, Hazel Virena (Hazel Virena Rinard ); Schwartz, Charlotte; Benham, Robert LeRoy, Sr.; Brooks, Amy; Baker, Nellie; Bolitho, Geneva; Blodgett, Dwain; Brain, Melvin; Campbell, Alice; Canale, Frank; Cassman, Nettie; Clark, Ruth; Cobb, Doris; Colby, Charles C.; Comfort, Edith; Cordier, Margaret; Cramm, Benjamin; Craven, E. Glenn; Davenport, Melvin; Dorman, Bernard; Edmunson, Donald; Edmundson, William; Edner, Mildred; Ellis, Helen; Evans, Gladys; Farinas, Lorena; Griffith, Ethel; Hanson, Elroy; Haworth, Rachel; Hockett, Elsie; Hull, Vera D.; Hunt, Esther; Huston, Marguerite Johnson; Jerome, Mark; Lingenfelter, Leonard; Lucas, George; Mardock, Wendell; May, Mattie; McConaughey, Clarence L.; Mitchell, Olive; Mylander, Ellwood; Neher, Galen; Neher, Marjorie; Olsen, Esther; Olson, Al; Parker, Floyd; Salazar, Jesse; Sanders, Ivan; Schwartz, Charlotte; Sherman, May; Shook, Mamie M.; Tycksen, Nute; Whittier, Thelma; Yergen, Blanche Elizabeth; Meeker, Elsie (Elsie Milner); Mills, Wilma Edith (Wilma Edith Witham); Mitcham, Lena; Jones, Elsie; Cady, Mary; Huston, Marguerite Johnson; Frazier, Lillian; Dorman, Bernard; Colby, Charles C.; Clark, Ruth; Charleson, Otto; Bolitho, Geneva; St. George, Isabelle
- 1992, 1/62
  Hawley-Kincaid, Ruth Emmaline; Jones, Elsie; Hoover, Ardis; Hoover, Lee
- 1993, 1/63
  Winters, Ralph Ervin; Smitherman, C.K.; Ogelview, Albert; Mayheew, One; Hawley-Kincaid, Ruth Emmaline; Hull, Vera D.; Badley, Mary; Birch, Robert
- 1997, 1/64
  Johnson, Elaine Storms; Drake, Rachel Ethel; Strang, Ester Ione; Broch, Connie; Penix, Dortha Elizabeth (Dortha Elizabeth Hanson); Newkirk, Sheldon Lowell; Morgan, Barbara Ralphs; Kunkel, Theresa I.; Kellum, Margaret Edith; Hubbell, Olaf Victor "Babe"; Hines, Joseph Wesley; Fuller, Estella Elizabeth; Bishop, James F.; Bartol, Thomas Russel; Anderson, Henry Robert, Jr.
- 1998, 1/65
  Ross, Alice; Bishop, Mary Elizabeth Ott; Woodward, Esther H.; Stevens, Edward F., Dr., President; Tucker, Hazel Ruth; Thompson, Earl; Sayles, Zola M.; Piersall, Willa; Persons, Helen; McNeil, Chester D.; Johnson, Maude Pearl Wright; Jones, Evan Anderson; James, Myron; Hendricks, Gertrude L.; Frost, Susan Irene; Flynn, Alice Rosebud Gee; Clouser, Lynn; Brandenburgh, Esther C.; Bartoll, Lillian Presnall; Barnes, Raymond
- 2003, 1/66
  Minas, Elizabeth Carey
- Unknown Dates, 1/67
  Dejmal, Alan Russell; Moore, George; Hibbs, George; Hardin, Milo; Headrick, Denver; Main, Margaret; Michener, Frank W.; Bassett, Willard; Rogers, Inez; Sims, Edgar Perry; Timson, Benny C.; Nicholson, S. Alice; Hibschman, Jesse; Cook, Dalton; Beals, Mildred; Baker, Irene; Johnson, Edna; Richey, Sterling; Kemper, Eugene; Craven, Charlene; Devaul, Marie Gregory Pop; French, Arthur; Hadley, Ivan; Haworth, Hanson; Meyers, Wendell; Ireland, Elsie; Berry, Jess; Roberts, Alvin; Reece, Joseph Gordon; Rose, Mary Thelma; Tuning, Charles; Smith, Richard; Judd, John Franklin; Johnson, Clarence; Ireland, George; Moore, Warren Wells; Knoble, Betsy; Rice, Eunice; Alteberry, Millie Barrett; Knight, Roy; Knutson, Gladys